A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, Accessions 2014-2015, RG 3 FA763
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, Accessions 2014-2015, RG 3
1972-2012
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund
FA763
53.04 Cubic Feet 94 standard record storage boxes, 4 legal size record storage boxes
Arrangement
The material remains in original order, with the records arranged into subgroups by accession and then each accession is further arranged alphabetically.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
Type of records include: Reports, publications, newspaper articles, correspondence, reprints, and photographs
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Grants, 1970-2012; 3.3; 43.2 Cubic Feet 95 standard document storage boxes 3 legal size document storage boxes Boxes 1-98
  - ABC Ulwazi, 1998-2001, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - ABC Ulwazi - Real Children - Digital, 1998 December-2005 October; 2014:031:001, 2014:031:002 (Item 2014:031:001, 2014:031:002)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - AFL-CIO Working For America Institute, Inc., 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AIDS and Adolescents Network of New York, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A-Projekt, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A-Projekt, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A Rocha-Christians in Conservation, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Abraham Path Initiative Inc., 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Conditions Governing Access
    "Restricted - Open in 2020"
  - Abyssinian Development Corporation, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Academy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Academcy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland (Folder 2) - Report on the Operations of the Academy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland - Published Material, 2002 February; 2014:031:003 (Item 2014:031:003)
    - Academcy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland (Folder 2) - 69 Pomyslow Na Aktywnosc Lokalna - Published Material, 2002 February; 2014:031:004 (Item 2014:031:004)
    - Academcy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland (Folder 2) - Dziataj Lokalnie - Published Material, 2002 February; 2014:031:005 (Item 2014:031:005)
    - Academcy for the Development of Philanthropy in Poland (Folder 2) - Zarys Historii Dobroczynnosci I Filantropii w Polsce - Published Material, 2002 February; 2014:031:006 (Item 2014:031:006)
  - Academy of Political Science, 1985, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Academy of Political Science - The China Challenge - Published Material, 1985 December-1991 December; 2014:031:007 (Item 2014:031:007)
  - Access: Networking in the Public Interest, 1989-1994, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14-16)
  - Access: Networking in the Public Interest Publications, 1991-1992, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17-19)
  - Action Against Crime and Violence Education Fund, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - ActionAid USA, 2003-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Adobe Theatre Company, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Adult Basic Education Development Services Trust, 1993-2004 (Box 5, Folder 23-27)
  - Adult Basic Education Development Services Trust, Tax Information, 1993-1996, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Adult Literacy and Basic Education and Development Foundation, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Advancement Project, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Advocacy Training and Resource Center, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Advocates for Environmental Human Rights, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Africa! Ignite, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Restricted-Open in 2021
  - African-American Institute, 1980-1993, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - African-American Institute, 1980-1993, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 36-38)
  - African-American Institute, Tax Information, 1970-1982, 1984, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 39-40)
  - African-American Institute, Bulletins, 1973-1974, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 41-42)
  - African-American Institute, Botswana National Commision on Education, 1975-1976, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - African-American Institute, Dana S. Creel, Staff Travel Award, 1979-1981, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - African-American Institute, Southern Africa, 1976-1982, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 45-46)
  - Museum for African Art, 1999-2001, 2005-2007, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Museum for African Art, 1999-2001, 2005-2007, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 47A)
    Restricted - Open in 2021
  - Museum for African Art, 1999-2001, 2005-2007, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Africare, 1972, 1979-1981, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Africare - Africare - A/V, 1980 June-1989 December; 2014:031:008 (Item 2014:031:008)
  - The After-School Corporation, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 50-51)
  - Aga Khan Development Network, 1983-1986, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 52-54)
  - Agricultural Development Council, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975-1976, 1978, 1982-1986, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 55-56)
  - Paul J. Aicher Foundation, Inc., 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - AID/Watch, Inc., 1997-2003 (Box 11, Folder 58-59)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance Foundation, Inc., 1999-2002, 2004-2008 (Box 11, Folder 60-61)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance Foundation, Inc., 1999-2002, 2004-2008 (Box 11, Folder 60A)
  - Air and Waste Management Association, 1992, 1997-2000, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Alaska Conservation Foundation, 1990-2000, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 63-67)
  - Alaska Conservation Foundation, 1990-2000, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 63A)
  - Alaska Conservation Foundation, 1990-2000, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 68-70)
  - Alaska Conservation Foundation, Tax Information, 1993-1999, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Alaska Marine Conservation Council, 1997-2003 (Box 13, Folder 72-73)
  - Alaska Marine Conservation Council, 1997-2003 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Albany Medical College of Union University, 2000, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Alerdinck Foundation, 1985-1994, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 76-78)
  - Alliance for the Arts, Inc., 2001-2002, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Alliance for the Arts, Inc., 2001-2002, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 79A)
    Restricted - Open in 2020
  - Alliance for the Arts, Inc., 2001-2002, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 80-81)
  - Alliance for Children and Families, Inc., 2000-2011 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    "Restricted - Open 2022"
  - Alliance for Children and Families, Inc., 2000-2011 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Alliance for Children and Families, Inc., 2000-2011 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Alliance for Children and Families, Inc., 2000-2011 (Box 16, Folder 85-86)
  - Alliance for Children and Families, Inc., Tax Information, 2001-2010 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Alliance for Children's Entitlement to Social Security, 2003-2010 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    "Restricted - Open in 2021"
  - Alliance for Children's Entitlement to Social Security, 2003-2010 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Alliance for Children's Entitlement to Social Security, 2003-2010 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Alliance for Children's Entitlement to Social Security, 2003-2010 (Box 17, Folder 91-92)
  - Alliance for Children's Entitlement to Social Security, Tax Information, 2004-2009 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    "Restricted - Open 2020"
  - Alliance for Justice, 1995-1997, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 94-95)
  - Alliance for Justice, 1995-1997, 2001-2003, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 94A)
  - Alliance for Nonprofit Management, 2000-2002, 2004, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Alliance for Nonprofit Management, 2000-2002, 2004, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 97-98)
  - Alliance Publishing Trust, 2007-2009 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Alliance of Resident Theatres/New York, Inc., 2005-2008 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Alliance to Save Energy, 1977, 1980-1984, 1991-1995, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 101-102)
  - Alliance to Save Energy, 1977, 1980-1984, 1991-1995, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 103-106)
  - Allied Media Projects, Inc., 2006-2008 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - America Abroad Media, 2005-2006, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, 1985-1993, 1996-1997, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 109-111)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Tax Information, 1973, 1981-1983, 1985, 1988, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Daedalus, 1995-1999, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Daedalus - Daedalus Winter 2001 - Published Material, 1999 March-2001 July; 2014:031:009 (Item 2014:031:009)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Daedalus, 1995-1999, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 114)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Daedalus - Daedalus Fall 1998 - Published Material, 1995 May-1999 February; 2014:031:011 (Item 2014:031:011)
    - American Academy of Arts & Sciences, Daedalus - Daedalus Fall 1995 - Published Material, 1995 May-1999 February; 2014:031:010 (Item 2014:031:010)
  - American Alliance for Rights and Responsibilities, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 115-117)
  - The American Assembly, 1988-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - The American Assembly, 1988-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 119-122)
  - The American Assembly, 1988-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 123-124)
  - The American Assembly, Tax Information, 1989, 1993, 1998, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 125)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 126-127)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1989-1997 (Box 24, Folder 128-132)
  - American Bar Association Fund for Public Education, 1970-1971, 1974, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 133)
  - American Center for International Leadership, 1985-1992, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 134-137)
  - American Center for International Leadership, 1985-1992, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 138-140)
  - American Committee for Aid to Poland, 1989-1996 (Box 26, Folder 141-142)
  - American Committee for Aid to Poland, 1989-1996 (Box 27, Folder 143-144)
  - American Conservation Association, Inc., 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 145)
  - American Council for the Arts, Inc., 1970, 1972-1975, 1977, 1979-1981, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 146)
  - American Council on Education, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 147)
  - American Council for an Energy Efficient Economy, 1998-2001, 2005, 2007, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 148)
  - American Council for an Energy Efficient Economy, 1998-2001, 2005, 2007, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 148A)
    Restricted - Open in 2022
  - American Council for an Energy Efficient Economy, 1998-2001, 2005, 2007, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 149)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1971, 1979, 1982-1984, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 150-153)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1971, 1979, 1982-1984, 1989-1996 (Box 29, Folder 154-155)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), Committee on Scholarly Communication with China, 1991-1997 (Box 29, Folder 156)
  - American Council on Renewable Energy (ACRE), 2002-2009, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 157)
  - American Council on Renewable Energy (ACRE), 2002-2009, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 157A)
    "Restricted - Open in 2020" "Restricted - Open in 2023"
  - American Council on Renewable Energy (ACRE), 2002-2009, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 158)
  - American Council on Renewable Energy (ACRE), Tax Information, 2002, 2004-2008 (Box 30, Folder 159)
  - School of American Ballet, 2003-2008, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 160)
  - School of American Ballet, 2003-2008, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 160A)
    Restricted - Open in 2023
  - American Dental Association Health Foundation, 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 161)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1989-1997 (Box 30, Folder 162-63)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1989-1997 (Box 31, Folder 164-168)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1989-1997 (Box 32, Folder 169-172)
  - American Farmland Trust, Tax Information, 1980-1995 (Box 33, Folder 173)
  - Museum of American Folk Art, 1978-1985, 1987, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 174-175)
  - American Forum, Inc., 2000-2002, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 176)
  - American Foundation for the University of the West Indies, Inc., 2007, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 177)
  - American Friends of the Royal Institution, Inc., 2004 (Box 33, Folder 178)
  - American Group Psychotherapy Association, Inc., 2002 (Box 33, Folder 179)
  - American Indian Artists (Amerinda), Inc., 2007-2009 (Box 33, Folder 180)
  - American Institute for Social Justice, Inc., 1997, 2003-2008 (Box 34, Folder 181)
  - American Institute for Social Justice, Inc., 1997, 2003-2008 (Box 34, Folder 181A)
  - American-Iranian Council, Inc., 2001-2008 (Box 34, Folder 182-183)
  - American-Iranian Council, Inc., 2001-2008 (Box 34, Folder 182A)
  - American-Iranian Council, Inc., 2001-2008 (Box 34, Folder 183A)
  - American Jewish Committee, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 184)
  - American Lands Alliance, 1997-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 185-186)
  - American Latvian Association in the United States, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 187-188)
  - American Littoral Society, Inc., 1998-2007 (Box 35, Folder 189)
  - American Littoral Society, Inc., 1998-2007 (Box 35, Folder 190-191)
  - American Littoral Society, Inc., 1998-2007 (Box 36, Folder 192-196)
  - American Littoral Society, Inc., 1998-2007 (Box 37, Folder 197)
    - American Littoral Society, Inc., Tax Information, 1995, 1998-2000, 2002-2006 (Box 37, Folder 198)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1970, 1972, 1980-1981, 1983, 1986-1987, 1993-1995, 1997-1998, 2000-2003 (Box 37, Folder 199-201)
  - American Oceans Campaign, 1995, 1997-2002 (Box 37, Folder 202)
  - American Oceans Campaign, 1995, 1997-2002 (Box 38, Folder 203-204)
  - American Opera Projects, 2004-2008 (Box 38, Folder 205)
  - American Prospect, 2004-2005, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 206)
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement, 2006-2009, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 207)
    "Restricted - Open in 2022"
  - American Symphony Orchestra, 2001-2004 (Box 39, Folder 208)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1994, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 209-212)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1994, 1996-2000 (Box 40, Folder 213-217)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1994, 1996-2000 (Box 41, Folder 218-222)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1994, 1996-2000 (Box 42, Folder 233-227)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1994, 1996-2000 (Box 43, Folder 228-232)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, Tax Information, 1985-1992, 1994, 1996-1999 (Box 43, Folder 233)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, Tax Information, 1985-1992, 1994, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 234)
  - American University in Bulgaria, 1999-2000, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 235-236)
  - American University of Beirut, 2003-2004, 2006, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 237-238)
  - American University of Beirut, 2003-2004, 2006, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 237A)
    "Restricted - Open in 2023"
  - The American University in Cairo, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 239)
  - Americans for Informed Democracy Corporation, 2004-2009, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 240-242)
  - Americans for Informed Democracy Corporation, 2004-2009, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 240A)
  - Americans for Informed Democracy Corporation, 2004-2009, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 243)
  - Americans for Informed Democracy Corporation, 2004-2009, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 243A)
  - AmericaSpeaks, Inc., 2002-2008 (Box 46, Folder 244)
  - AmericaSpeaks, Inc., 2002-2008 (Box 46, Frame 245-247)
  - AmericaSpeaks, Inc., 2002-2008 (Box 46, Folder 247A)
  - Amherst College, 1980, 1984-1988 (Box 47, Folder 248-250)
  - Amigos del Museo del Barrio, Inc., 2002-2008 (Box 47, Folder 251-252)
  - Amigos del Museo del Barrio, Inc., 2002-2008 (Box 47, Folder 251A)
  - The Apollo Theater Foundation, Inc., 2006-2010 (Box 47, Folder 253)
  - Appleseed Foundation, Inc., 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 254-255)
  - Applied Research and Development Institute International, Inc., 1995-1999 (Box 48, Folder 256)
  - Aquinas Housing Corporation, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 257)
  - Architecture Research Institute, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 258)
  - Arizona Board of Regents, 1991-1997 (Box 48, Folder 259-261)
  - Arizona Board of Regents, 1991-1997 (Box 49, Folder 262-266)
  - University of Arizona, 1989, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 267)
  - Arms Control Association, 1990-1995, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 268-271)
  - Arms Control Association, 1990-1995, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 272-276)
  - Art in General, Inc., 2002-2007 (Box 52, Folder 277-278)
  - Art in General, Inc., 2002-2007 (Box 52, Folder 277A)
  - Art 21, Inc., 1999-2002 (Box 52, Folder 278-279)
  - ArtLink, 2006-2008 (Box 52, Folder 280)
  - Arts & Business Council, Inc., 2002 (Box 52, Folder 281)
  - Arts for Art, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 52, Folder 282)
  - Arts for Art, Inc., 2003-2007 (Box 52, Folder 282A)
    "Restricted - Open in 2018"
  - Arts International, Inc., 2002-2004 (Box 53, Folder 283)
  - Arts of Peace, Inc., 2004-2008 (Box 53, Folder 284)
  - ArtsConnection, 2005-2008 (Box 53, Folder 285)
  - ArtSpace Project, Inc., 2006 (Box 53, Folder 286)
  - Ashoka, 1985-1999 (Box 53, Folder 287-288)
  - Ashoka, 1985-1999 (Box 54, Folder 289-294)
  - Ashoka, 1985-1999 (Box 55, Folder 295-296)
  - Ashoka East Central Europe Program, 97-146, 1993-1999 (Box 55, Folder 297)
  - Asia Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 55, Folder 298-300)
    - Asia Foundation (Folder 298) - Conference background papers on diskette (2 copies) - Digital, 1998 April-2002 August; 2014:031:012, 2014:031:013 (Item 2014:031:012, 2014:031:013)
  - Asia Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 56, Folder 301-305)
  - Asia Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 57, Folder 306-310)
  - Asia Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 58, Folder 311-316)
  - Asia Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 59, Folder 317-319)
  - Asia Foundation, Tax Information, 1975-1981, 1986-1987, 1991-2000 (Box 59, Folder 320)
  - Asia Foundation Translation, Service Center, 1979-1981, 1984, 1986, 1990-1992 (Box 59, Folder 321)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2005 (Box 59, Folder 322)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 323-327)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2005 (Box 61, Folder 328-333)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 334-338)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2005 (Box 63, Folder 339-344)
  - Asia Society, 1990-1998, 2001-2205 (Box 64, Folder 345-350)
    - Asia Society (Folder 348) - India Briefing 1900 - Published Material, 1990; 2014:031:014 (Item 2014:031:014)
  - Asia Society, Tax Information, 1970-1986, 1988-1995, 2001, 2003, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 351-352)
  - Asian American Writers' Workshop, Inc., 2002-2007, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 353-354)
  - Asian American Writers' Workshop, Inc., 2002-2007, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 353A)
  - Asian Americans for Equality, 2003-2005 (Box 65, Folder 355)
    - Asian Americans for Equality - Topography of War: Asian American Essays - Published Material, 2003 December-2005 March; 2014:031:015 (Item 2014:031:015)
  - Asian Cultural Council, 1984, 1989-2009 (Box 66, Folder 356-360)
  - Asian Cultural Council, 1984, 1989-2009 (Box 67, Folder 361)
  - Asian Cultural Council, Tax Information, 1989-2008 (Box 67, Folder 362)
  - Asian Institute of Technology (AIT), 1987, 1989-1994 (Box 67, Folder 363-366)
  - Asian Institute of Technology (AIT), 1987, 1989-1994 (Box 68, Folder 367-369)
  - Asian Institute of Technology (AIT), 1987, 1989-1994 (Box 68, Folder 368A)
    Restricted from scholarly access-Confidential material
  - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation, Inc., 1990-1999 (Box 68, Folder 370)
  - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation, Inc., 1990-1999 (Box 69, Folder 371-375)
  - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation, Inc., 1990-1999 (Box 70, Folder 376-381)
    - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation (Folder 379) - Singing the Same Song - Published Material, 1995; 2014:031:016 (Item 2014:031:016)
  - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation, Inc., 1990-1999 (Box 71, Folder 382-385)
  - Asian NGO Coalition Research Foundation, Inc., Tax Information, 1990-1992, 1994-1997, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 386)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 387)
    "Restrcited - Open in 2023"
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 388)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 389)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 390)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 72, Folder 391-392)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 73, Folder 393-398)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 74, Folder 399-403)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., 1983-1995, 1997-2009, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 404-405)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Tax Information, 1971-1983, 1988-2008 (Box 75, Folder 406-407)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Tax Information, 1971-1983, 1988-2008 (Box 75, Folder 406A-407A)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Environmental Security Policy Project, 1994-1996 (Box 75, Folder 408)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Environmental Security Policy Project, 1994-1996 (Box 76, Folder 409)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Global Interdependence Initiative, 1997-2006 (Box 76, Folder 410-413)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Global Interdependence Initiative, 1997-2006 (Box 77, Folder 414-416)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Nonprofit Sector and Philanthropy Program, 1988-2003, 2005-2007 (Box 77, Folder 417-419)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Nonprofit Sector and Philanthropy Program, 1988-2003, 2005-2007 (Box 77, Folder 417A)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Nonprofit Sector and Philanthropy Program, 1988-2003, 2005-2007 (Box 78, Folder 420-424)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Nonprofit Sector and Philanthropy Program, 1988-2003, 2005-2007 (Box 79, Folder 425-430)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Nonprofit Sector and Philanthropy Program, Publications, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 431-432)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Program on Communications and Society, 1992-1994 (Box 80, Folder 433)
    - Aspen Institute Inc. - Program on Communications and Society - Television/Radio News and Minorities - Published Material, 1992 December-1994 June; 2014:031:017 (Item 2014:031:017)
    - Aspen Institute Inc. - Program on Communications and Society - Television for the 21st Century: The Next Wave - Published Material, 1992 December-1994 June; 2014:031:018 (Item 2014:031:018)
    - Aspen Institute Inc. - Program on Communications and Society - Television and Elections - Published Material, 1992 December-1994 June; 2014:031:019 (Item 2014:031:019)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Program on the U.S. and the World Economy, 1990-1993 (Box 80, Folder 434-435)
  - The Aspen Institute, Inc., Program on the U.S. and the World Economy, 1990-1993 (Box 81, Folder 436-438)
  - Aspira, Inc., 1970-1974, 1980, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 439)
  - Associates of the National Agricultural Library, 1991
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York Fund, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 81, Folder 441)
  - Association Dah Theater, The Center for Theater Research, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 442)
  - Association for Energy Affordability, Inc., 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 82, Folder 443)